townscript.com 2015-04-12

# Privacy Policies | Townscript

## Information Collection

We collect information during registration, use of the services site, communicating with site members, admin, using content, content upload to our site. We also receive information about your IP address, cookies and pages you visited. Such informations are collected to provide best service, research, and overall product experience.

## Information Sharing

We will always obtain your prior specific consent before we share or disclose your personally identifiable information to any partner, and user. We are also accountable to disclose user information and the contents of the Accounts to the local law enforcement authorities under specifically defined circumstances. In case Townscript service gets merged or acquired, we will be informing on the website about such developments.

In case your profile is public, or your details are in public domain in our site, you will receive unsolicited messages from users in townscript.com and from external sources.

When you have opted for receiving related information, we will use your information to show you relevant advertisements, contents, events from us and our partners. Access to your name, email address and private details is restricted to our employees who need to know such information in connection with our services and are bound by confidentiality obligations. 

## Cookies

We use 'session' cookies for a browser session, we also store cookies in your computer to access your login information, and preferences. We use cookies to enhance your experience of our services.

## IP Address

When you visit townscript.com, we receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer, operating system information, browser information and name of your ISP. This information is used to improve our service offerings, we are also legally accountable to pass the same information to legal authorities when requested. We also advanced web analytics, which provides information such as the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going.

## Links from Our Website

We have many pages containing external links. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of such externally linked websites. We are not responsible for the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide Personal Information, without assuring yourselves of the privacy policy of external linked websites.

## How Secure is Your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your Personal Information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in your Account.

Our employees also sign confidentiality agreements to use your data for product enhancement, bug fixes and for services only. 

## Notification of Changes

When there are significant changes to the privacy policy, the same will be posted on our websites in order to keep you informed of any changes in nature of information collected, manner of collection, use and sharing of information.

## Conflicts Between Privacy Policy & Terms

At any time, when there is a conflict between the terms of service and the privacy policy, the Terms shall control.We don't provide service to children under age 16, therefore we don't collect informations and privacy policy makes no provision for children's use of the site.

If you have any questions, suggestions and comments regarding this privacy policy, please. contact us at service@dyulok.com .
